igoldrush.com 2017-01-03

# iGoldrush Privacy Policy

We understand and respect that online privacy is important to users of iGoldrush (“Site”).  This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business, and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services (“Services”) offered by iGoldrush (“Authorized Customers”).

**What is Personally Identifiable Information?**  
Personal Identifiable Information refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, and credit card information.  Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?**  
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We may collect additional information from our Authorized Customers including the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell. 

**What organizations are collecting the information?**  
In addition to our direct collection of information, third party advertisers and service vendors may also collect information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third parties use such information. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information. 

**With whom may the information may be shared?**  
We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf. 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by iGoldrush is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties except for use as indicated above. 

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us by using the website contact form.

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than a certain amount of time, we may automatically log the Authorized Customer off. 

**How does iGoldrush use login information?**  
iGoldrush uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, operating systems, browser types, and referring links, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?**  
iGoldrush has entered into and may continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors. Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility. Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.

**Would iGoldrush disclose Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law?**  
We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena, or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers. 

**How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**  
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place.  iGoldrush and its related companies will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences. 

**How can Visitors and Authorized Customers correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by using our website contact form.

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**  
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure. 

**What about links to other web sites?**  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
